https://aerofred.com/pages.php?template=privacy_policy

Type ID and go to plan
Go!
Radio Modeller
More...
Top Flite
More...
Veron
More...
Thunder Tiger
More...
Walt Mooney
More...
Foamies
PDF format Plans
CAD format Plans
SPAD
More...
3D Printed Model Airplanes
Vintage Mags, Catalogs...
Type order tracking code
Track!
Login/Register
Home Privacy policy
Keyword SearchPick only one from each group and keep in mind that we are in the process of editing all the plans so only the plans already edited will show up.
Class
Autonomous-UAV X
Type
Airplane
Glider
Sailplane
Helicopter
Auto-Gyro
Wingspan
Less-Than-50cm (20in)
50cm-To-75cm (20in-To-30in)
75cm-To-100cm (30in-To-40in)
100cm-To-125cm (40in-To-50in)
125cm-To-160cm (50in-To-63in)
160cm-To-200cm (63in-To-79in)
200cm-To-260cm (79in-To-102in)
More-Than-260cm (102in)
Wing Dihedral
Dihedral
Anhedral
Polyhedral
Gull-Wing
Inverted-Gull-Wing
Motor Type
CO2-Powered
Weight
Less-Than-50g (1.75oz)
75g-To-100g (1.75oz-To-3.5oz)
100g-To-200g (3.5oz-To-7.0oz)
200g-To-300g (7.0oz-To-10.5oz)
300g-To-500g (10.5oz-To-17.6oz)
500g-To-1000g (17.6oz-To-35.2oz)
1000g-To-1500g (35.2oz-To-52.9oz)
2000g-To-2500g (70.5oz-To-88.1oz)
2500g-To-4000g (88.1oz-To-141.0oz)
More than 4000g (141oz)
Landing Gear
Flying-Boat
Floatplane
Mono-Wheel
Quadricycle
Skid
Taildragger
Tandem
Expert
About the Keyword Search ToolAs plans are edited the keywords above are attributed to them.
When you pick keywords from the panel above you are asking the system to return you the plans that contain those keywords. Each plan will contain the keywords you choose and the plans descriptions will not be searched.
To remove a keyword just delete it from the search field, please remove it entirely or the search results will not be so good.
Help to edit plans
Privacy Policy
Information Collection
Information Usage
Information Protection
Cookie Usage
3rd Party Disclosure
3rd Party Links
Our Contact Information
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address
or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form
or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
• To improve our website in order to better serve you.
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.How do we protect visitor information?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
We monitor and block full IP ranges when suspicious activity is detected.
We use an SSL certificate
We do not deal with detailed personal information or financial information at all. Payments are processed by Paypal with whom you must have a signed agreement and you have it or you won´t be able to pay.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us e data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
• Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
• Keep track of advertisements.
• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If users disable cookies in their browser:
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
Login automatically to the site when you visit us.
Periodic banners with important information regarding the site will be displayed on each page load if you turn off the cookies.
Third Party Disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy.
The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. -
See more at: https://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
• On our Privacy Policy Page
Users are able to change their personal information:
• By emailing us
How does our site handle do not track signals?
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we allow third party behavioral trackingCOPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control.
The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13.Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify the users via email
• Within 7 business days
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
• NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
• Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can
• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email. and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us.
Last Edited on 2018-05-20 for GDPR compliance.
Downloading the camel plansCheck your "Downloads" folder.
About AeroFred.comAeroFred has been providing model airplanes and boats plans to the modeling community since March 2006, the site has grown from a few hundreds of plans to the thousands you see today with contributions from out members.Sharing new plans is a great form of contributing but if you don´t have plans to share but still want to help we also accept Paypal donations that we use to pay for the server and traffic monthly fees and help our fellow members to pay for the postage on new plans they send us to scan and share at the website.
ContributeFind plans on the web and share them here, share the link to this page on forums, help us to edit plans listings...
Upload a Plan
Site Editors
Link to this page:
SubscribeDonate a small amount monthly to help with the server bills and download traffic overcharges.
Paypal Subscribe
$3.00 EUR
$5.00 EUR
$10.00 EUR
$20.00 EUR
$50.00 EUR
DonateDonate once to help us with the site´s expenses.
About the camel Plan
This plan is 391.4 KB and was shared by our member Submitted to AeroFred on 24/03/2015 18:32 in the PDF Bitmap Wood Plans from Magazines category.It has been downloaded 46 times by fellow modelers from around the world.
Show AppreciationSubmitted to AeroFred has spent time working on this plan so you can have it now, you can always leave him an appreciation message.
Share your BuildsSubmitted to AeroFred will surely like to see what you have build from his plans... You can share your builds at our Forum under the Build Logs section.
Close
Top
